[Disclaimer: Characters, locations,
and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Fanboy]
[≠ just "a fan who is a man"]
[= a male fan]
[whose liking transcends into passion,
so much so that it is part of their life]
Being a fan might be total nonsense
in some people's eyes.
But to me,
it's love given
without expecting anything in return.
Watching him do
what he loves from afar
is enough to make me happy.
To Nine,
the highly skilled actor
whom I regard as the light of my life:
Your existence
makes me truly happy.
For that reason...
please live such a happy, happy life.
From this fanboy of yours!
[Mr. Fanboy Series]
Wan, where are you?
They're already strutting so much
they might as well do next year's lineup.
Tell them to catch up with
this year's plan first.
Nine hasn't arrived, has he?
Not yet.
But I think he'll be here any minute now.
Get a move on!
Okay, okay.
I'm hanging up now.
And here they are, the pair of lead actors
from 'Friend Benefit'!
- Hello.
- Hello, hello.
Hello, there.
Alright, please introduce yourselves.
Who do you play in this series?
I play Jai.
What about you, sweetie?
My character's name is Pik.
Pik.
Every pairing on our red carpet
is marvelous today.
Next up, let's hear it
from another project we have,
'UNKNOWN LOVER'!
Hello there.
International fans,
don't miss it for the world.
Yes, for all international fans,
please be kind, and also, please welcome
our new series project
because we can't wait to see
the 'UNKNOWN LOVER' pilot.
- 'Friend Benefit.'
- It's 'Friend Benefit.'
There.
- In Thai, it's "Just friends."
Just friends, huh?
That's all?
Pinky swear?
Wan, damn it, come here!
Come on over here!
Whoa!
They held such a grand event this year.
Must be tons of series to come.
Think they'll be able to keep up?
Jeez, who could ever?
No company could ever keep up with it.
As long as my bias gets a series,
I'm fine with it.
Alright,
the final pairing
that many have been waiting for
has arrived.
Excuse me,
allow me to use the chair.
Get up there
and share the photos with me.
Please put your hands together
for Nine, Nopphanat Wongwiboon,
this year's 'Rising Star,'
the absolute man of the hour.
And of course,
wherever Nine is, there's Third,
Tharit Charatdecha,
who was awarded 'Best Supporting Actor'
and has second-to-none acting skills.
Together as 'Rising Star Partners,'
they are surely
a very promising pair to keep an eye on.
And the series starring
Third and Nine as male leads is
'The Deep Between Us.'
Please make some noise once again!
- Hello, North.
- Hello.
I heard this is your first series
as a producer.
- As a new face,
- That's right.
how do you feel?
I'm incredibly thrilled.
- It's my first time doing this.
- Sure.
It's very different from my acting career,
- Mm.
- but well... I'm sure that
I'll do just as great a job
as I did when I was an actor.
One thing I must ask.
Right.
How did you manage
to get the rights to the novel?
I've heard that
the author felt really worried
and didn't want it adapted into a series.
Yes.
It was a hard process
to acquire the rights to this novel.
Absolutely no joke.
But I showed them how sincere I was
and assured them that
we'd do everything
- to the best of our ability.
- Mm... Right.
I guess they saw how determined we were.
As for our male leads,
ThirdNine...
Third and Nine,
how are you feeling?
How have you prepared
yourselves for this series?
Right,
Copter is very determined
to become a competitive swimmer,
so I learned how to swim
and studied
the character's feelings in depth
so I can convey them
as realistically as possible.
Right, I agree with Third,
as we've done a heap of research.
Also...
I'd like to express
how truly important everyone is.
We're here today
because of all your support.
Right, Third?
Wow, do you see that? Do you?
That's a little too tight.
Hey! Are you...
100% playing the part of Copter?!
It's like they came straight
out of the novel cover or something.
True that!
Besides, their skills are guaranteed by...
the 'Rising Star' award
and the 'Best Supporting Actor' award.
With these accolades,
how could they not be amazing?
And you've formed
a joint venture with Da Xiang for this.
- Precisely.
- Right.
Uh, so this novel
has so many Thai fans
and international fans.
Therefore, Da Xiang
was interested in investing with us.
So, I'm expecting
cute moments from this series.
Oh, rest assured.
We'll certainly go all out.
I'd prefer it
if everyone focuses on the acting
since I believe that there are many factors...
that go into making a good series,
not just the cute moments alone.
Right.
We're looking forward to it.
Such an interesting series.
Damn it, he's humiliating Nine!
But I think Third is right.
Nine was being too extra!
Absolutely no one deserves Third, ever.
I don't think so.
Your fave is incredibly lucky
to have Nine as his partner.
Apart from acting,
he can sing and dance,
and he's an all-round Rising Star.
Plus... your fave
actually humiliated
someone mid-interview.
Is that what a decent person does?
And what's your problem?
I was just chatting with my girl
when suddenly,
you stuck your nose in, acting all psycho
and even hyping up
your fave so desperately.
Take Nine's side or whatever.
As for me, I'm on Third's side!
Right?
Dear fans!
The merch has now been restocked.
This is gonna be the last batch.
If it runs out, it runs out!
Come on in!
Come on in, come on in.
Please.
How does that taste?
Whoa! This bitch!
Settle down.
- Settle down. You'll get a chance to...
- Whoa, calm down, ma'am.
- Please settle down, guys.
- Please settle down.
- Everyone, settle down.
- You'll get your chance to claim it!
- Oh, thank you very much.
- Settle down, settle down,
- Come, come, come.
- Stop!
Hello.
I'd like two of each of Nine's merch items.
Would you also like Third's?
No, thank you.
Fabulous!
A solo stan, not here for the pairing.
Rock it.
Are you Nine's fanboy?
Isn't that cute?
Uh...
It's for my friend.
- Right!
- "It's for my friend."
So where's this friend of yours?
Over there!
There...
- Over there, huh? Okay.
- Yes.
So that will be all?
Okay, I'll take those off.
- Sure thing.
- Oh, okay.
Two of each of Nine's merch items, yes?
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Those in the back, please stay calm.
- Alright, all of Nine's merch.
You'll get your chance to claim it.
Rest assured.
Please rest assured.
Jay, I'm dying to unbox it.
Boy, you're way too obsessed!
Is it even worth it?
"Worth it" is an understatement.
And what's this?
Are you...
going to the gathering looking like that?
What's your deal?
I've brought a change of clothes.
What kind of person are you?
You seriously have a spare outfit?
Hey!
I ride a motorcycle.
When it rains,
I need my spare outfit
if I get soaked, don't I?
Man, whatever.
I'll go see my sweet Pink.
Bye-bye.
Getting my daily dose of Pink.
- Sure.
- My daily dose of Pink.
- Pink...
- Sure, go get your fill.
Better go get changed.
Where on earth is the restroom?
Third.
Do I have to sign you up
for a Media Training 101 class?
What did I do wrong?
I said nothing but facts, didn't I?
I'm here as an actor,
so acting is what I'm selling.
You're selling both the "pairing"
and the "acting," boy.
Besides,
as you stand next to Nine,
you have to show him respect.
You gave that interview
like you have
zero emotional intelligence.
After how you reacted to Nine,
how are the fans gonna ship you now?
If you'd like to stay in this industry...
you need to understand how it works.
Don't get too big for your britches.
The label you're wearing
is "BL actor."
But if you don't wanna do it,
all you have to do is retire
from the BL industry.
Just make sure...
your mom won't beat your ass.
That's enough.
That's it.
Hey.
Don't stress it
because what you thought
was so damn cool
just landed us at No. 1 trending.
[#TheDeepSeries]
[#ThirdNine]
Ooh...
I really wanna unbox it!
Alright, I'll just do it.
[STAFF ONLY]
[Nine]
[Special Box Set]
Oooh!
That's adorable.
The insane quality, though...
Ooh!
Shit...
I spoke too soon.
Wan!
Where on earth are you changing clothes?
Pink and I are already done
with the gathering.
Right,
just stay with Pink for now.
I'm taking care of something.
What is it?
You changed and went
to unbox the thing, huh?
I knew you would!
What do you mean?
I have self-control.
Plus,
even if I did,
it's not like I did anything wrong!
It is.
It's not!
It is,
since the fans can't access this area.
Sunny,
send in the guards, please.
There's a stalking sasaeng in here.
Hello, Wan.
Why did you hang up?
Jay, help me!
What was that?
Help you from what?
That damn Third called the guards on me!
Oh! So that's why he sounded familiar.
Stop thinking about it and help me!
I'm in here somewhere!
You need to find a way in.
Am I the only one here or something?!
Where in the hell are all the guards?!
Susan,
please give Nine a touch-up.
Nine...
Who are you?!
A sasaeng.
A sasaeng...
You stalking sasaeng...
Whoa!
Who the hell is this?!
- A fucking sasaeng, bitch!
- Huh? A sasaeng?!
- A sasaeng!
Susan!
- Catch...
- Argh!
Argh!
Ah!
- Argh! You sasaeng.
- Ugh!
A sasaeng?
- Go to that end!
- Catch him!
- Get him!
- Rotate it.
Arghh!
I got him! I got him!
No, you got me!
He's over there!
Rin!
- Huh?
- Come help!
Bitch!
Gotcha, you fucking sasaeng!
- That's my neck!
- Ugh!
- Grab onto the rack!
- Uh, my bad.
- Yeah!
- You sasaeng...
Why are you so fucking strong?!
He's rotating it!
I'm getting dizzy, ugh!
- Three, two, one!
Where are you going?!
You think you could get away from me?!
Nab him...
How did you get in here?
Is everything okay?
The cavalry finally arrives.
Jeez... Took you long enough.
Take him!
Get him good.
People like this
don't belong in society!
Sir, take him away.
Rin,
- Huh?
- Susan,
stay here with Nine.
I'll deal with him.
Sure, sure, sure.
Go make sure he's dealt with.
These damn people...
Hey!
What's a sasaeng?
Sir, you've got it all wrong!
Third,
go wait in the room.
I'll take care of that stalking sasaeng.
He'll get a piece of me.
Grab me.
Ugh...
Now, go.
Off you go.
Wasn't that too far?
You two, turn him over to the cops.
I'm not a stalking sasaeng.
You're not...
Then what is that?
The merch... is for
my proxy shopping service.
As for the chair,
I'm a photographer for hire.
Whoa!
What are you doing to my friends?
Dude...
They're saying I'm a sasaeng.
Why did you become a sasaeng?
Jay, you bastard!
Be serious!
Uh...
What proof do you have
to accuse him of being a stalking sasaeng?
True, true, true.
Your friend snuck into
the artist's dressing room, that's what.
Jeez... So what?
He just entered the wrong room.
How does that make him a sasaeng?
Where's the proof?
Mm, where?
There it is,
the complete and blatant proof
that you're a stalking sasaeng.
What?!
Are you just accusing him now?!
Anyone can buy merch, can't they?
I'm a paying customer.
You should thank me.
Sir!
Are you gonna believe
this dragon lady or me?
Don't listen to them.
Hand them over to the cops.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Ooh... should I go live?
This way, the whole world will know that,
in management's eyes,
the fans are at the bottom of the system.
It's gonna blow up so hard
it'll knock #TheDeepSeries to the bottom.
I think the world deserves to know.
Go on!
Take us away!
I'm gonna scream!
Loudly, by the way!
Yeah, tell them being a fan is wrong!
True!
That buying merch is wrong!
Exactly!
Still, you're desperate
for the fans' support.
Yeah, I'm so confused.
It's basically free labor!
Ooh, so what now?
What are you gonna do?!
Ugh!
I don't wanna make it a big deal
and ruin a good day.
Just don't show
your faces around me again.
Next time,
I'll be the one going live!
You're not gonna be the ones who get to do it.
Please get them outta here.
Hey...
We can walk.
We'll strut out in style.
Is my merch damaged?
If it is, just pre-order another one.
"Pre-order," do you even hear yourself?
That's gonna take a lifetime.
Jeez... they've improved
the system nowadays.
Sometimes, it depends on
the manufacturer, too.
Give them a chance.
It's not gonna take a couple of days.
So...
what happened?
Fill me in.
I'm not ready to!
Jay?
So this dude snuck off
to unbox his merch on the rooftop,
came across Third,
ran into Nine's room,
and taken away as a stalking sasaeng
by the guards Third called.
Sir, you've got it all wrong!
My dear angelic boy,
what a good person you are.
And you...
Why did you become a sasaeng?
You've taken it too damn far.
I'm!
Not!
A!
Fucking...
Sasaeng!!
Ugh... You jerk!
I'm going home.
View, take care of your older brother.
Wan.
Wan?
Wan!
[The Deep Between Us]
I'll trade it for Third's photos.
I know you got some shots of him.
Do you want it or not?
I only have one.
Send it over.
Ooh!
Stunning!
He's both talented and handsome.
You're good at taking photos.
I'll give you that.
[Trending]
[#TheDeepSeries]
♫Baby, feel the drive♫
♫The thrill hittin' right♫
♫Let's go for a ride♫
♫Here we go, here we go,
chitty-chitty, clang-clang♫
[Casting Call]
♫Here we go, here we go,
chitty-chitty, clang-clang♫
♫Oh, clang-clang♫
♫Down with the beat,
deeper we go!♫
♫Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah♫
♫Here we go, here we go,
chitty-chitty, clang-clang♫
I called Pitch to discuss
yesterday's incident
and have already hired a PR team.
Had we waited for you to make your move,
you wouldn't be able
to do it if you tried.
Do whatever you want, Mom.
Good.
Since you've realized
that you're incapable,
letting me take care of it
is the right call.
Just fulfill your duty properly.
I sincerely hope that
you can manage that much
on your own for once
because if you
keep making mistakes,
I won't be able to be...
so nice to you anymore.
[I was too in character yesterday
probably because Noel was next to me;
please stay tuned to see us
in 'The Deep Between Us']
Wan!
What the heck?
Why are you in my room?
Look.
Hey, where are you going?
Home. Move!
Wait, wait, wait.
You can't just ride
a motorcycle to Ayutthaya.
Some ten-wheel truck
is gonna run you over!
- Get a grip and call Mom first, will you?
- Why bother?
No need to call
when the entire shop is in ruins.
No, stop!
Can you just get a grip?
You're not thinking straight,
so how could that help anyone?
Give me that.
Go.
It's nothing, kids.
[Mom]
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
Aunt Paed has already sent me photos
of our house in ruins.
Aunt Paed...
She's a master of
sticking her nose in, huh?
I...
fell for a call-center scam.
Huh?!
It was that day when I called you, Wan,
asking...
if the money was enough,
and you seemed confused.
I remember that day.
But I already told you
that I wasn't in need!
Exactly.
That's how I found out I'd been scammed.
So...
Why didn't you check
if the name on
the bank account matched Wan's?
Well, he said...
that I had to wire it
to Wan's friend's account.
But he sounded exactly like Wan.
He called me and said,
"Mom, I need money for an emergency."
That's why I was quick to wire the money.
Okay.
How much did you send them?
It was over multiple transactions...
It was 700,000 baht.
We emptied out our account.
So why did the scammer damage your shop?
They already got so much money anyway.
When I couldn't
manage the cash flow, I...
borrowed some money
from a loan shark, sweetie.
And how much is that?
Just focus on your studies, guys.
Mon and I will handle this.
We've gotta help each other, right?
Alright, alright.
Even if I forbade you,
you'd help anyway.
So just
don't push your limits, okay?
Please?
Dad and I are gonna close up the shop now.
[Mom]
Where are you gonna find the money?
I don't know.
Let me help, too.
No need.
Just focus on your studies.
I'll take care of it myself.
I'll manage.
Hey,
any job I could take on?
I need to pay off a debt.
What debt?
Don't mind it.
Just know that I have one.
How quickly do you want it?
As quickly as possible.
You wanna...
try auditioning for this?
[Casting Call]
Being an actor is
the easiest way to make money.
And with your personality,
you're a good fit for Sky.
Take a look.
What?
Why would I even audition?
Just give it a try.
I've
even been to one,
but I didn't make the cut, damn it...
Ugh, it's a no from me.
Trust me on this one.
For this kind of stuff,
you only have to look the part.
And you have the look for it.
Big eyes
and a sweet-looking face.
What do they call it?
A conventional bottom.
Learn how to grind
using your looks for once.
I know!
I know that I look handsome,
but that won't cut it
if I suck at acting, right?
Since when do I know how to act?!
Who on earth is born with acting skills?
They all take acting classes.
If you make the cut,
they're gonna sign you up for workshops.
Nope.
You get paid
and get to act with Nine.
A big W, isn't it?
That way, you won't
always have to be on the hustle.
It's a win through and through.
Ugh!
Cut it!
A shit ton of people
will audition for that role.
If I actually auditioned
and got the role,
I'd stuff my face with dog food!
You said it, Wan.
No takesies-backsies.
Go ahead and pick
whether you want the beef flavor
or the liver one.
Or maybe...
the chicken in gravy one.
None of those!
Wan,
I saw your post looking for gigs.
The seniors are looking
for a photographer. Interested?
I am.
It's for...
the 'The Deep Between Us' audition.
Sure thing.
Uh... How much does it pay?
How does 3,000 baht sound?
Okay.
Okay, it's a deal.
- I'll forward you the deets, then.
- Alright.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
"The Deep Between Us."
[Casting Call]
I'm not auditioning!
You'll definitely get a role.
You look so handsome today.
Here comes Ton.
Ton,
please come this way.
- This way, please.
- Ooh, hello, there.
- Hello there, everyone. Hello.
- Ooh, Ton's looking so good!
Ooh, as handsome as ever.
Hello!
- Three of them?
- Three of them, totally.
So many gorgeous men here today.
Ooh, go ahead
and take some photos, sweetie.
Thank you so much.
Hello.
We'll go see what's there first. Come on.
Your boy looks pretty handsome.
Is he auditioning for a featured extra?
What can I say?
The main roles
have already been snatched
by some boorish people.
Pitch,
you're still so good
at seeking attention, though.
Maybe give it a shot.
I won't charge you for it.
So handsome!
- Who's that?
- Ooh, how good-looking.
Uh, boys,
- could you step aside for now?
- I'll continue with the photos.
Allow me to take photos
of the main leads.
Come on.
Nine, Third, over here!
Hello!
Please.
So handsome.
Hello.
Yes, keep striding.
Hello, hello.
- Strike a pose.
- Give... Give us a cool pose.
It's Renji.
Is the wait long?
Hello.
You look good.
Right.
Wut, this way, please.
Thank you.
Renji, let's go.
- Aw. How cute!
- What's your name?
I'm Time.
Aw, so cute.
- What a cutie patootie.
- Kids these days, I adore them.
Wut!
Hm?
A hidden gem!
Alright,
have a chat with him.
Just make sure he isn't signed
with any company.
Alright,
then...
Here you go.
Put the name tag on Renji.
And you've been
holding onto that for ages!
Hello, kid.
Are you here to audition?
No, I'm not.
I'm here to take photos.
Right.
Pardon my manners.
Let me take another look.
What an ideal bottom.
Hey...
Are you signed with anyone?
Uh...
No.
Come with me.
Uh...
Where are we going?
Just come with me.
Kid,
remove your mask for me.
Ma'am,
I have photos to take.
Today
will forever change your life.
I'm only asking you to...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
How about this?
I'll pay you,
and I'll find them a new photographer.
But I'm only asking you
to spend a day with me.
I'll give you 2,000 baht.
5,000, then...
Okay.
But you've gotta
wire me the money first.
Alright, sure. I'll do it right now.
Do it.
[Mom]
What else do I have to do?
Put your stuff down,
first of all.
Okay.
That includes your backpack.
Take off your outer shirt
and your cap.
Okay.
Alright. Now, take a seat.
Ready?
Hello, I'm Renji,
auditioning for Heart.
Copter!
You're... a scum.
You used Noel.
How could you?
You think that's gonna make you
the apex predator of the industry?
You're nothing but a crappy swimmer.
You're gonna fade away
from the industry soon enough.
Both you...
Between you and your friend...
after all this time
and the rest of what happened...
This industry doesn't need you!
Just quit!
Quit.
I said quit!
And don't even think of setting foot
back in the industry again.
Thank you.
Three, two, one.
Ay!
What do you think, Lhao? Fabulous?
- Go ahead. Best of luck.
- Do your best, kids.
Ooh...
Who is that?
Who?
Who is that, Lhao?
So handsome.
Ooh...
Ooh, that's a chef's kiss bottom!
The press is here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Smile.
Do it.
Ooh, oh?
He's under Cher...
Look at all the gorgeous boys they have.
Lhao, look at that girl!
- Ooh...
- Lhao...
Hey...
Wan, right?
Yes.
I thought you weren't gonna come, sweetie.
Look, they were all asking
for you in the back,
wondering when you were coming and all.
Uh...
But I didn't...
Is this your name, sweetie?
[Wan]
Wanna tell me what this is about?
Who did this?
Jay,
you applied for the audition for me?
Yeah, just in case.
It's gonna be fine.
There are, like, a thousand applicants.
They're not gonna care.
I was gonna give you a call,
but the number on file
only has nine digits,
- so I couldn't reach you.
- Right...
Ladies,
give him a minute to discuss
some private matters, please.
- Sure thing.
It's his.
He's totally gonna get
the role of "Sky."
You're straight
out of the description, sweetie!
Ma'am, there's one spot
he forgot to fill out.
It's... his agency.
- Oh...
- Does he have one?
It's 'Our Houses.' He's with Wut.
It's better to have a home.
It's more comforting that way.
Trust me.
Fabulous, sis.
If you hadn't been with one,
I would've started my own agency.
Where have you been
all our lives, hiding that look, sweetie?
Here's an audition script
for Sky, sweetie.
- Sure thing.
- Alright...
The role is definitely his.
He's perfect for the description.
- Thank her.
- You've got this.
Let's go.
Say thank you to the nice lady.
- Uh... thank you.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Bye-bye.
Best of luck. Bye-bye.
- Alright.
Let's do a bit more touch-up
on your face and your hair, shall we?
- He's gonna land the role of Sky.
- For sure.
Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- Thank you.
Alright, one down.
- It's Time, right?
- It is.
Right now, it's no one else but Time.
Only Time.
- Obviously.
- True.
Here, let's go ahead and mark him.
Drawing an asterisk.
We'll go with Renji.
- Huh?
Huh?
Did you get the name wrong?
Him.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
He's right.
It's Renji.
Hey?
Hey.
By the look of him,
it's like he glided right off the novel cover.
I mean, Time is alright,
but Renji looks the part.
As for the acting, no sweat.
Leave it to me
- Mm-hm.
- because it's my job.
Okay, then.
I'm really relying on you for this.
Didn't seem like his acting was any good.
Ugh...
People learn through trial and error,
so make sure you give him directions.
But count on me.
I'll make sure he performs well.
Sure, just do your best with your part.
There's one person left
auditioning for Sky.
Please come in.
And you are...
Wan, right?
Yes.
Focus.
No rush.
Whenever you're ready, though.
[Wan]
"Huh... So this is the promising young shark?"
"Huh... Is this
the promising young shark
Coach praises so much?"
All I can see is a fucking loser.
Why? Can't handle some sting?
"What?
Why are you staring at me? Are you angry?
Or you can't handle the truth I said?"
Terrible.
What me to show you superior acting?
Show me how it's done
since you're so good.
From what I've seen
in the series, you're not all that.
Come on.
Fine.
Run the scene with me, then.
But you'll have to improvise it.
You first.
I'm giving you a head start.
Go ahead.
You think you're so good.
Are you sure
you made it here because of your skills?
I think, just maybe,
it's your family pulling some strings?
That's why you're here.
You're absolutely not a good match
for your partner.
And why do you think
I'm not a good match for him?
At least, I never have
to go to desperate lengths
just to approach someone.
But I can see you're already busting a gut
just to be seen by someone,
just to impress them.
But let me tell you something.
You have a shitty way of doing it!
How is it shitty?
I'm just here to audition.
- If you don't know a thing...
- Do I really have to know?
You wouldn't understand.
You're playing dumb.
Did you come up with that yourself,
or was it your family?
Hm?
Go home and ask your family
how the fuck they raised you...
to be so deceitful.
Keep your mouth off my family.
You did that to mine first.
If you wouldn't like it done to you,
maybe don't do it to someone else,
or people might say...
that your family is incapable.
If you're saying,
"my family helps with everything,"
then that means
your family hasn't helped shit!
Oh, gosh!
Why?
Oh, my God.
Yeah!
My family is not doing well.
We're always in trouble.
You have no idea
what the fuck I've been through.
You have no idea how hard I've tried
to give my family a better life.
You were born rich!
What the fuck would you know?
In your mind,
you're so perfect!
You're the best!
No one's better than you!
Be careful, though.
With that fucking nature and sharp tongue,
your glory days might not last long.
But you have nothing to worry about, huh?!
Your family is well-off, anyway.
You seem to know everything about me.
Are you a fan?
Hm?
All this effort...
Is it to get a sneak peek at the celebs?
Are you my fan?
Or Nine's?
Watch your behavior, though,
or people will call you
a "stalking sasaeng."
What now?
Do you want me to tell everyone
who you really are?
I recognize you...
Why did you become a sasaeng?
- You've taken it too damn far.
- I'm!
Not!
A!
Fucking...
Sasaeng!!
Hey, Luang. Go check on Wan.
Right.
No, no, Luang...
No need.
Let Third do it.
I think you took it a bit too far.
What if it got out
and did a number on the series?
That was so impulsive, though.
- Hey...
- I mean...
Alright, come whisper it to me.
That's what we do for private stuff.
Wan, the boy who just auditioned for Sky...
I mean, it'll work, but...
- I'll have a hard time directing.
- So lit.
Wan!
How was it?
I'm not going to pass for sure.
Huh?
Wan!
Our noodle shop...
It was 700,000 baht.
We emptied out our account.
Focus on your studies, guys.
Do you want me to tell everyone
who you really are?
Who are you?
A sasaeng.
You were born rich!
What the fuck would you know?
I can give it all up so that...
Your family hasn't helped shit!
Why are you here?
Leave me alone.
Hey.
Hey... Hey!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
If you want it to go away,
listen to me.
Right now, you need to get your breathing
back to normal.
Try this method.
Keep your focus here,
on my finger.
Think of it as a flower,
whatever breed it might be,
then take a deep breath
as though you're smelling it.
Slowly.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Hold your breath.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Blow on the flower.
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Keep doing it
until you feel better.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Hold your breath.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Blow on the flower.
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
As though you're smelling it.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Hold your breath.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
You feel better now?
[The Deep Between Us]
Wan.
Jay, why are you here?
Where's Wan?
In his room.
Why did you bring dog food, though?
- Just in case it's a fluke.
- Huh?
Go in. The door isn't locked.
Wan! Wake up, man.
Wake up!
What?
Someone called.
Give them a call back.
Why hand me your phone?
It's yours, not mine.
Cher called.
What?
But why did she call you?
He gave her my number, that's what.
Here.
Hello?
Is this really you, Wan?
Yes.
So what's up?
Shit, you made the cut?!
Made what cut?
Well, he auditioned for
a series called 'The Deep Between Us.'
The one...
starring ThirdNine?
Yes!
Shit!
So that means you're gonna be a star!
♫Even though it's a long way to the end♫
Welcome to 'Our Houses,'
where every dream...
comes true!
This is Wan, our new boy.
Hello, Wan.
Such a familiar face.
Have you heard about Nine's stalker?
I'm so happy that
I get to work with you, Nine.
I'm your fan.
Still smiling, huh?
You wasted everyone's time.
I don't like you.
I don't like you, either.
I don't care why you joined the industry,
but I hate how unprofessional you are.
♫To reach the summit,
the more I climb, the colder♫
♫The closer I get to seizing it, the lonelier♫
♫Just like a star so bright,♫
♫The further from the dark nights,♫
♫The more ablaze, primed to burn down♫
♫Just like how I lost touch
with people along the way,♫
♫The more steps I took,
the more desolate I became♫
♫As though I'm cursed in my soul♫
♫So deeply, I wound everyone
who makes me whole♫
♫No one's heart♫
♫Do I want to tear apart♫
♫By my own hands♫
♫But I'm ready to leave it all behind♫
♫Just so I could trade it for the sky♫
♫Even though it pains,♫
♫Even though the trace of tears remains,♫
♫No pain, no gain, no pain, no gain♫
♫Even though it's a long way to the end♫
♫I'm ready to leave it all behind♫
♫Just so I could claim the sky♫
♫I'd sacrifice my being♫
♫Without looking back and regretting♫
♫No pain, no gain, no pain, no gain♫
♫For the end I yearn for in my veins♫
♫I'm hell-bent on moving heaven and earth♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]